Experience Earth like never before.
A Beautiful Planet is a documentary, adventure,
family film directed by Toni Myers.
A breathtaking portrait of Earth from space, providing a unique perspective and
increased understanding of our planet and galaxy as never seen before.
Made in cooperation with the National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), the film features stunning footage of our magnificent blue
planet — and the effects humanity has had on it over time — captured by the astronauts aboard the International Space Station (ISS).
Self - Narrator (voice), played by Jennifer Lawrence.
Self (uncredited), played by Samantha Cristoforetti.
Self (uncredited), played by Scott Kelly.
Self (uncredited), played by Kjell Lindgren.
A Beautiful Planet is an IMAX Entertainment documentary produced in collaboration with
NASA and filmed aboard the International Space Station by astronaut crews.
Narrated by Jennifer Lawrence, it was produced and directed by Toni Myers.
The film offers distinctive views of Earth and provides insight into the day-to-day
activities of the crews, captured over fifteen months aboard the space station.
It also examines the impact of humans on Earth and its
potential analogues in the Milky Way.
A Beautiful Planet was first released in the United States in 2016 and later
aired in the United Kingdom, Australia, New Zealand, and Russia/CIS.
The film explores themes of earth, space station, time lapse photography,
aerial photography, international space station (iss).